foreign
[Music]
Beatrix Potter quotes is what heaven can
be more real than to retain the spirit
world of childhood I must agree that if
there is one thing that always feeds my
soul it is stories
that is why I work at a little book shop
in my town selling stories receiving
stories and being surrounded by strange
and Whimsical and wonderful worlds all
encompassed inside a binding and put and
put on a Shelf
[Music]
foreign
habits have definitely gotten worse
since I started here I get a discount
and free books and for a book lover it
is a recipe to find yourself quickly
drowning in stories
I've definitely had to control myself a
bit but today was different I received a
gift card for my birthday so it was time
to pick up a new stack to bring home
as I hear often echoed within the walls
of this shop there is no such thing as
too many books
[Music]
foreign
I returned home with several new books
and some bags of wildflower seeds to
cast on the snow in early spring
[Music]
I have a variety of old used books I was
given this year as well as some newly
purchased this book seems so sweet and
it is quite old which I enjoy and I also
got one of Emily Martin's very early
books because I wanted to support her as
her art is very enchanting to me
as an early gift for my brother I got
him a book featuring his favorite animal
the otter as well as another children's
book for the daughter of a friend I
recently had a customer recommend this
book so I thought I'd give it a go
though I don't read too much romance I
also really want to read the life of
elves I don't know too much about it and
I'm very curious
and of course I had to purchase Jackie
Morris's newest books everything she
does fills me with Wonder and she holds
a special place in my heart her
watercolors always inspire me to paint
my Daydreams
foreign
inspired by all these books I decided to
make some wood burned bookmarks for my
future reading Adventures I admit that
the nib I had on this pen was quite dull
and old so the project turned out rather
rotten but I thought I'd include it
because it's a good reminder that our
creative attempts may not always work
out
but that only means that the end result
has taught us something and therefore it
has value and for that we can be
grateful
[Music]
thank you foreign
so apart from the books that I recently
purchased in order to support my small
town my bookstore business but of course
my reading problem
I wanted to share with you my reading
list for December because maybe it will
inspire you with some book ideas or it
will just get you in a cozy mood to
spend the evening reading or partaking
in any other crafts or hobby that you
enjoy this time of year I know there are
other people who feel this way but I
don't think there are too many adults
who enjoy graphic novels that are
intended for children but I do so I
absolutely love the movie The Song of
the sea if you have not seen it on
Netflix it is enchanting and the same
creators also made a couple other movies
in the similar style and atmosphere and
so one of them recently was called wolf
Walker I already watched it while song
of the sea is definitely my favorite
this one was still enchanting and
beautiful to watch and there is a
graphic novel version of it so I thought
that I would read this one I'm sure that
if it's anything like the movie it is
going to be very funny but also touch
upon some very important aspects to our
culture especially in regards to Nature
preservation and respect for wild
animals I'm also going to be trying out
this graphic novel called the daughters
of ease I want to say I'm not sure I'm
saying that right but it seems to be
kind of a haunting rather spooky Tale
But the illustrator is absolutely one of
my favorite illustrators I love all the
work she does and so I'm excited to give
this one a try even though I have heard
it is rather spooky I will also be of
course rereading one of my favorite
fantasy books of all time which is
Nevermore the trials of Morrigan Crow
this book exists in a world that has an
amazing holiday celebration including
Father Christmas and the Yule Queen the
disc description of the magical
celebrations in December in this book
are
just so enchanting and always get me in
the mood for the holidays I'm also going
to be reading a Nest for Celeste it's a
very simple children's book but it
features a little mouse that befriends a
boy I've heard it is rather a serious
book so I'm not quite sure what to
expect but the illustrations are
adorable so I thought I would give it a
go I do of course plan to be reading
some books uh meant for adults but I
haven't quite decided on my reading list
yet and I also am not a very fast reader
it takes me uh weeks sometimes to finish
a single book and I find it very
difficult to speed read so I actually
don't get through that many books I
think I'm just dedicated so I do end up
getting through more than I always think
I will I do not have the physical copy
in my hands right now but I am also
reading the body keeps the score which
is a non-fiction book about trauma and
how it expresses itself in the physical
body it's definitely not a light read so
that one so far has been very moving and
cathartic and fascinating I highly
encourage everyone to read it especially
if they have had experiences related to
anxiety or other mental health
challenges in their life I think that is
it I doubt I will get through all the
books that I'm planning to read but I am
choosing a lot of graphic novels this
month which is rather unusual for me I'm
looking forward to it so I think I'm
going to spend the rest of the day
probably reading because I am back from
work and I have the rest of the day off
and the bookstore is an extremely
physical job and I am tired I think I'm
gonna start with some graphic novels so
I'm sending you all my love I hope you
have a cozy and enjoyable evening and
find a little bit of time to do what you
love and treat it as a sort of ritual an
important part of self-care and Mental
Health Management so take care and I
will see you very soon
[Music]
foreign